PERSONAL DETAIL:

Name : Dani Lesmiadi

Date of Birth : Bandung, February 11th 1981

Nationality : Indonesian

Education : Bachelor Degree, University of Computing

(UNIKOM), 2004

Address : Jl. Sawo 2 Ujung, no. 64C, Cipete-Jakarta

Selatan

Email Address : dani.lesmiadi@gmail.com

Phone : +62-8122-44-3582



I am an enthusiastic and organized individual. Through previous roles I have gained experience in project managing and an understanding for the responsibilities linked to this role. I have the ability to prioritize well and understand what tasks should come first and how to complete them in the most effective manner.

Previous administrative roles have taught me how to prepare documents and how to coordinate different events and projects. My solid IT skills will also allow me to create documents as I have a vast knowledge of many IT packages. I have great communication skills, which would enable me to liaise with central services, contractors and staff. I work extremely well and efficiently when part of a team, which is key in this role as there is always a need for managing and leading change when required.

I have an eye for details, which means that issues such as Health and Safety will always be a main priority and I have the ability to respond to any sort of situations in the best way possible. I am hard working and give one hundred per cent to everything I do. I am committed and trustworthy and always willing to learn and pass on any knowledge that I have to others.

Please check out my profile at http://www.magnificom-id.com/dani-lesmiadi

KNOWLEDGE

SOFTWARES:

- 1. Ms. Project
- 2. Photoshop
- 3. HTML
- 4. CSS
 - Bootstrap
 - Bulma
 - Materilize
 - Vuetify

NETWORKING:

- 1. CISCO router Management
- 2. Manage & Un-Manage Switching Device
- 3. Wired Local Area Connection / Installation
- 4. WIFI Connection / Installation

5. Javascript

- Native/Plain Java script
- Jquery
- Node Js
- Vue Js
- React Js
- React Native

6. Server Side

- Plain PHP
- Laravel
- CodeIgniter

7. Databases

- My SQL
- Mongo DB
- 8. Linux Server
- 9. NGINX
- 10. Version Control (GIT)

WORK EXPERIENCE

SiteCoordinator

August 2015 – November 2017

PT. Surya Kusuma ~ *Building and Engineering Contractor* Jakarta

Responsibilities:

- Discussing requirements with the potential clients
- Kick of Meeting with potential clients
- Assessing the environmental impact and risks connected to projects
- Judging whether projects are workable by assessing materials, costs and time requirements
- Drawing up blueprints, using Computer Aided Design (CAD) packages
- Provide the Bill of Quantity (BOQ)
- Preparing bids for tenders, and reporting to clients, public agencies and planning bodies
- Undertaking technical and feasibility studies including site investigations (e.g soil durability, drainage, electricity, etc.)
- Liaising with clients and a variety of professionals including architects and subcontractors
- Making sure sites meet legal guidelines, and health and safety requirements.
- Managing, directing and monitoring progress during each phase of a project
- Plan ahead to prevent problems and resolve any emerging ones
- Coordinate and direct construction workers and subcontractors
- Review the work progress on daily basis
- Ensure quality construction standards and the use of proper construction techniques
- Prepare internal and external reports pertaining to job status

- Reconcile check-list according to Bill of Quantity (BOQ) with client
- Hand overing finished product to the client/s

Facility Coordinator

July 2012 – August 2015

Weatherford Indonesia - http://www.weatherford.com Bekasi

Responsibilities:

Maintenance & Facility Management Roles:

- Maintain and monitoring subsidiary office such as Talavera Based, Narogong Based, Balikpapan Based, Duri (Riau) Based
- Maintain office and workshop equipment, physical space and telecommunications systems for a Building or Base.
- Schedule preventative maintenance, respond to urgent maintenance calls and participate in the creation of emergency preparedness plans

Administrative and Management System Roles:

- Building the Web based Requisition Portal system based on previous share point system
- Developing Web based Requisition Portal system for organized and manageable repair and maintenance request
- Managing and Full filling departments/business units requests or requirements
- Applying for required environmental permits (Hazardous Substances)
- Monitoring tools & equipment certification and calibration
- To monitor and follow up CPAR (Corrective Preventive Action Request) and NCR (Non Conformance Record) status throughout all division and help departments to close out on time.
- Coordinate weekly Operation meeting with Business Units and Business Supports

Weatherford Indonesia - http://www.weatherford.com Jakarta

Responsibilities:

- Installing and configuring computer hardware, software, systems, networks, printers and scanners
- Planning and undertaking scheduled maintenances and upgrades
- Communicate to clients or computer users to determine the nature of problems
- Responding to breakdowns such as trouble on servers, data and voice.
- Investigating, diagnosing and solving computer software and hardware faults
- Repairing equipment and replacing parts
- Supervising 3 rd party junior engineering and technical staff (IT)
- Agreeing time-scales based on project requirements.
- Obtaining replacement or special components, fixtures or fittings
- Checking computer equipment for electrical safety
- Maintaining records of software licenses
- Managing stocks of equipment, consumables and other supplies

IT Infrastructure

November 2016 – August 2019

PT. Eptco Dian Persada - Assigned for BP Tangguh LNG Project West Papua

Responsibilities:

- Managing Hardware, Software inventory and Licenses. Supporting users (Application & Hardware Support).
- System Windows 2003 Server Active Directory Administration.
- Firewall Administration and Monitoring (Cybercam & Cisco ASA).
- IP Phone configuration (Cisco Products).
- Server Installation such as Physical Server or VMware (Blade Server).
- Storage Area Network Administration.
- VLAN Administration, Switching and Routing. Lotus Domino Server and Lotus Notes Client Administration.
- Local Area Network (LAN) and Wide Area Network Monitoring.
- Internet User Administration(Microsoft ISA Server).
- Internet link migration, Upgrade Metro Ethernet bandwith.
- Symantec BackupExec Administration & Monitoring.
- IT Network Drawing and Cost Estimation for new Project plan.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science, Informatics University of Computing (UNIKOM) - Bandung, West Java – Indonesia 2014

TRAINING

•	CCNA Intensive - Interconnecting Cisco Network Device - ICND v4.0, Bandung	2010
•	ITIL - IT Infrastructure Library v. 3.0, Jakarta	
•	Weatherford APAC Certified ComCAM Torque Bucking Unit Operator and	2010
	Calibrator, Kemaman – Malaysia	2013
•	Fire Fighting, Internal Weatherford – Jakarta	
•	First Aider, Internal Weatherford – Jakarta	2014
•	Fundamental if Rigging, The Crosby Group - Jakarta	2014
•	Heavy Rigging Application, The Crosby Group - Jakarta	2014
-	ricary rigging Application, the crossy Croup - bakarta	2014

PERSONAL INTERESTS

- Music
- Photography
- CAD Design
- Web Apps Development using PHP, MySql, Javascript and other various frameworks Portfolio: http://magnificom-id.com